{
    "subject": "resource/1995\u201396_Liverpool_F.C._season",
    "predicate": "property/team",
    "object": "resource/Chelsea_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "The team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was Chelsea F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885894060134888,
            "question": "Was Chelsea F.C. part of the Liverpool F.C. team in the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9804234504699707,
            "question": "What was the team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9722865223884583,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Chelsea F.C. and the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534767270088196,
            "question": "Against which team did Liverpool F.C. compete in the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9440069198608398,
            "question": "Which club played against Liverpool F.C. in the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9147858023643494,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Liverpool F.C. and Chelsea F.C. in the context of the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9013240933418274,
            "question": "Can you describe the football matchup between Chelsea F.C. and Liverpool F.C. in the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8998647928237915,
            "question": "Who were Liverpool's opponents during the 1995-96 season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8737996816635132,
            "question": "Who were the teams involved in the 1995-96 football season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908596992492676,
            "question": "In what season did Chelsea F.C. play against Liverpool F.C.?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was Chelsea F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8208_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the teams involved in the 1995-96 football season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8208_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were Liverpool's opponents during the 1995-96 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8208_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the football matchup between Chelsea F.C. and Liverpool F.C. in the 1995-96 season?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8208_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8208_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "That's incorrect.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**\n\nChelsea F.C. was indeed the opposing team to Liverpool F.C. in the 1995-96 Premier League season, according to the results listed in a table from that season."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was not Chelsea F.C., but rather Liverpool F.C. themselves. Therefore, the answer remains:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes, incorrect as the team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was not Chelsea F.C., but Manchester United F.C. won that season.\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "No"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was not Chelsea F.C., but rather Liverpool F.C. itself, as indicated by the provided player stats, transfers, and match results of the 1995-96 season.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text details the statistics and results for Liverpool F.C. during the 1995-96 season, not Chelsea F.C.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided mentions Chelsea being W12 D14 L12 in the Premier League in 1995-96, with a corresponding league finish of 11th, which contradicts the statement that the team for the 1995-96 Liverpool F.C. season was Chelsea F.C.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}